<u>Émilien</u> BAI

Computer Science and Engineering Student - INSA Lyon

Education

2012-2014

About

Väderleden 3A - 169 976 33

Luleå Sweden

emilien.bai@insalyon.fr +33 (0)6 04 42 50 18

Driving License International Mobility 23 years old

Languages

English Advanced (TOEIC 970/990) German Intermediate (B1) Swedish Notions French Mother Language

Programming

JavaScript (Angular, NodeJS), Solidity, Java, C#, Go, MongoDB, SQL, Shell, OpenGL (basics) Arduino

Diverse

Linux, Windows, Eclipse, Intellij Idea NetBeans, Android Studio, Visual Studio, LATEX, Git, SVN Autumn 2016 Exchange student

Luleå University of Technology

Computer science program and Swedish courses

2014-2017 Computer Science and Engineering student

Theatrical technician option

Undergraduate program in sciences engineering INSA Lyon

Theatrical technician option

2012 French Baccalauréat S with honors Lycée Champagnat (69)

Specialization in mathematics and physics

Experience

02-07 2017 Luleå University of Technology, SV

Research Internship

INSA Lyon

- Design and implementation of a reward system for collaborative care of elderly.
- Development of a back-end based on smart-contracts using distributed ledger technologies and a mobile application as a blockchain "wallet".

05-08 2016 Foxstream, Vaulx-en-Velin, FR

Software Engineer Intership

- Update of Foxtool, software used for CCTV camera placement simulation.
- Creation of cameras point of view 3D simulation (C#, OpenTK, GLSL)
- · Inclusion of common design patterns in the existing version.

May 2016 INSA Lyon, FR

Group project "Potholess"

- Creation of a working prototype of an embedded system in a 10 days sprint.
- · Automatic detection of roads imperfections and data collection.

06-08 2015 XLR Project, Lyon, FR

Software Engineer Internship

- Entire development of a Java application from specifications to release.
- · Conversion of analog signals into MIDI messages.
- Integration with a drum set to create an interactive video installation.

2015-2016 INSA Lyon, FR

Maths tutoring

• Tutoring lessons for a group of 4 undergraduate students of INSA Lyon.

Summers 13-14Sicoly, St Laurent d'Agny, FR

Seasonnal work

Order picking. & Team management as a substitute.

Summers 09-12 Gilles Gaudin, Arboriculturist, FR

Seasonnal work

Seasonnal work as a fruit picker.

Volunteer experience

2015-2016 Commission de Gestion de la Rotonde (CGR)

Vice president

Management of the theater of the campus of "la Doua": schedule, material park management, rentals.

2014-2016Festival Karnaval Humanitaire, logistic team

Technician

Light equipment research and gathering, assembly of the stage and the technical facilities during the festival.

Interests

Theatrical technician: lightning for theater plays, dance shows, sound technician for concerts. Realization of short films. Amateur photographer.